<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>viral on </title>
    <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/tags/viral/</link>
    <description>Recent content in viral on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://michaelcgrady.github.io/tags/viral/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Italian Christmas Meal 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/italian-christmas-meal-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/italian-christmas-meal-2021/</guid>
      <description>The word “breakfast” comes from the action of “breaking the fast” that occurs overnight after your last meal of the day and continues until you eat the next morning. According to the american diabetes association, about 34 million people in the united states — both adults and children — are living with diabetes, and an additional 1.5 million people are diagnosed every year. Every item on this page was chosen by a woman&amp;#039;s day editor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Handprint Ornaments Diy 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/handprint-ornaments-diy-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/handprint-ornaments-diy-2021/</guid>
      <description>These projects are perfect for a rainy saturday afternoon, and many are easy enough for you to build with kids. Many of us put off planning a halloween costume only to realize suddenly that halloween is just days away. We used bonbons yarn in lime from the brights set and green with emerald sparkle f.
  10+ Kids Halloween Handprint and Footprint Ideas | BeesDIY.com from www.beesdiy.com  Create memories as you put together these diy christmas ornaments from hgtv magazine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>9 Ft Garland 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/9-ft-garland-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/9-ft-garland-2021/</guid>
      <description>Shop for 9 foot pre lit garland at bed bath &amp;amp; beyond. Specification this luxurious 9ft garland is part of our cream and gold themed range and is a great way of decorating your home this christmas there are a . Northlight pre lit heavily flocked pine 9 ft.
  Glittery Gold Pre-Lit 9 ft. Garland - Christmas Garland at Hayneedle from images.hayneedle.com  English gardens premier collection size: This artificial pine garland has dense, rich, green foliage and sturdy branches, making it ideal .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Outfit Couple 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-outfit-couple-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-outfit-couple-2021/</guid>
      <description>Wear some casual for the party: Go bold or go home. You won&amp;#039;t find many specific costume instructables here, but you will find props, basic costumes, makeup effects and more to st.
  Christmas Vacation - Cousin Eddie | Chris Lister | Flickr from c1.staticflickr.com  Add in some criteria like funny and matching and you&amp;#039;r. As you will likely spend time gathering with friends and family at different parties, one way that you can make … Dress in red tights, dresses, red winter jackets, scarves, and green to mix it up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Felt Santa Ornament 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/felt-santa-ornament-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/felt-santa-ornament-2021/</guid>
      <description>Created in collaboration with pottery barn kids, this adorable felt santa ornament is a perfect reminder that santa is making a list (and checking it twice) . Target/holiday shop/christmas/christmas ornaments &amp;amp; tree decorations/felt : This homemade ornament is no sew and makes for a wonderful gift.
  32 Homemade DIY Christmas Ornament Craft Ideas - How To Make Holiday from hips.hearstapps.com  Celebrate the holidays with more santa!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Edible Reindeer Food 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/edible-reindeer-food-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/edible-reindeer-food-2021/</guid>
      <description>The term “food desert” paints an accurate picture of a dire situation that many americans face daily. And many of those waste products your kidneys filter out come from the foods you eat. Adults love this convenience food because it makes cooking that much simpler, and kids love the mildly terrorizing thrill of popping the can.
  Cute Food For Kids?: 37 Edible Reindeer Crafts from 3.bp.blogspot.com  But many of the most delicious foods in the world also happen to be the.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Large Christmas Gnomes 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/large-christmas-gnomes-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/large-christmas-gnomes-2021/</guid>
      <description>Santa claus, christmas, christmas tree, garden gnome, tree,. I couldn&amp;#039;t find a good tutorial sharing how to make a large gnome so i made a detailed video . The nose can be made from a bowl and spray painted in skin color.
  DIY Evergreen Gnomes - Christmas porch | Easy christmas diy, Faux from i.pinimg.com  Get into the christmas spirit with the christmas extra large gnome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St Nikolaus Day 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/st-nikolaus-day-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/st-nikolaus-day-2021/</guid>
      <description>Patrick’s day, you might think of green beer, shot glass necklaces that say “kiss me, i’m irish,” and everyone suddenly talking about how irish they are. So put on something green, grab a beer and help the irish celebr. In may 1980, the largest terrestrial landslide ever recorded triggered a lateral blast at mo.
  Gifts And Treats! Free St. Nicholas Day eCards, Greeting Cards | 123 from i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Tree Gnome 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-tree-gnome-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-tree-gnome-2021/</guid>
      <description>09/12/2019 · my christmas tree gnome was finally coming together. Pull the tines of the tomato cage together snugly and wrap them in floral wire to secure them, bringing the tomato cage to a nice point. The christmas gnomes have become an …
  there. | Diy dollar tree decor, Dollar tree jenga, Dollar tree diy crafts from i.pinimg.com  Instructions for gnome christmas tree. 09/12/2019 · my christmas tree gnome was finally coming together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Wood Carvings 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-wood-carvings-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-wood-carvings-2021/</guid>
      <description>I made this christmas wreath from just a few meters of maple veneer edging. Printable wood carving patterns make it easy to get started on a wood carving hobby. Want to make something by hand that will be sure to be remembered?
  large brown vintage ceramic deer fawn figurine / christmas reindeer from i.etsystatic.com  Check out this simple guide to get you star. I made this christmas wreath from just a few meters of maple veneer edging.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January 7 Christmas 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/january-7-christmas-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/january-7-christmas-2021/</guid>
      <description>Nasdaq/other data delayed 15 minutes unless indicated. Advertisement are you a new year baby? Last week, i shared margaritas, tacos and guacamole with three friends i’ve known since i was 17.
  Lucy on Gardening: Nov 21, 2011 from 3.bp.blogspot.com  Advertisement are you a new year baby? Do you have a january birthday? Copyright © 2021 investorplace media, llc. Do you have a january birthday? Last week, i shared margaritas, tacos and guacamole with three friends i’ve known since i was 17.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gold Tree Decoration 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/gold-tree-decoration-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/gold-tree-decoration-2021/</guid>
      <description>For living unbreakable ornament set adds elegance and charm to your tree. Customize it with your name or a word that expresses the true meaning of the holiday. This christmas decorate your real or artificial christmas tree in all things gold!
  30 Creative White Christmas Tree Decorating Ideas from i1.wp.com  A unique twist on the traditional christmas tree. 20/12/2021 · rose gold christmas tree decoration ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diy Pallet Snowman 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/diy-pallet-snowman-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/diy-pallet-snowman-2021/</guid>
      <description>Whether it’s a table, kitchen wall or calendar, you can use numbers, letters or pictures to make any space your own. Maybe you&amp;#039;re trying — and failing — to get a stain out of a piece of clothing or maybe you’re trying to figure out the best way to make diy repairs that won’t cost you a fortune. For readers that have children or.
  15 Easy DIY Christmas Signs for a Festive Front Porch â¢ The Garden Glove from www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green Fairy Lights 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/green-fairy-lights-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/green-fairy-lights-2021/</guid>
      <description>11/12/2021 · fairy light trees are inspired by the fairy trees that date back to celtic times in irish folklore. 5 out of 5 stars. Create the perfect atmosphere with our fairy light tree.
  40 Romantic And Whimsical Wedding Lighting Ideas - Page 2 of 2 - Deer from www.deerpearlflowers.com  Green fairy lights,anjaylia 16.5ft/5m 50leds led string lights st. 5 out of 5 stars. Green led battery operated fairy lights, rustic wedding decor, room decor, 6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holiday Food Ideas 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/holiday-food-ideas-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/holiday-food-ideas-2021/</guid>
      <description>Your kidneys are powerful filtration systems that remove toxins from your blood to keep you healthy. Check out below for information on foods that can help raise “good”. The world is full of culinary wonders.
  Over 40 of the BEST Rock Painting Ideas - Kitchen Fun With My 3 Sons from kitchenfunwithmy3sons.com  Fast food is quick and easy, but usually processed. Of all the foods that come in cans, it’s hard to believe that soft, flaky biscuits are one of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grinch Kitchen Decor 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/grinch-kitchen-decor-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/grinch-kitchen-decor-2021/</guid>
      <description>Chefan grinch christmas decorations, 10.5 grinch ornaments,. Seuss classic how the grinch stole christmas can create the best grinch christmas tree with these ornaments &amp;amp; decorations. The grinch pancake molds, $17;
  Amazon.com: Department 56 Grinch Village Max and Cindy-Lou Who from images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com  Shop target for grinch christmas you will love at great low prices. Why do i love my kitchen decor? Chefan grinch christmas decorations, 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>White Tinsel Garland 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/white-tinsel-garland-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/white-tinsel-garland-2021/</guid>
      <description>Buy 108in white tinsel garland and other decorative holiday decor from our affordable decor, unique home furnishings &amp;amp; accents at serene spaces living. Find many great new &amp;amp; used options and get the best deals for 4 x snow white luxury deluxe chunky christmas tinsel garland tree decoration 2m at the best . Shop wayfair for the best white tinsel garland.
  1/2&amp;quot; White Iridescent Tinsel Craft Pom Poms - Pom Poms - Kids Crafts from factorydirectcraft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joann Christmas Tree 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/joann-christmas-tree-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/joann-christmas-tree-2021/</guid>
      <description>We may earn commission on some of the items you choose to buy. With a wide array of palm tree varieties, you’ve got lots to consider before you buy a palm tree for your yard. The best time to prune is almost always when the t.
  Christmas Cotton Fabric Random Trees on Plaid Glitter | JOANN from www.joann.com  Sure, a freshly cut christmas tree smells great — for a few weeks while you’re also dealing with the high cost, the hauling home, the dog drinking its water and the eventual crispy fire hazard it becomes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heb Christmas Meals 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/heb-christmas-meals-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/heb-christmas-meals-2021/</guid>
      <description>Get great meal help and so much more at wegmans.com. The most delicious meal ever! Christmas is just six days away and to help you prepare the perfect dinner, heb cooking connection joined bvtm to share a few recipes.
  H-E-B Holiday Meals | Order Christmas Dinner Online | HEB.com from images.heb.com  Browse thousands of items with prices and create your shopping list with our online builder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michaels Christmas Clearance 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/michaels-christmas-clearance-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/michaels-christmas-clearance-2021/</guid>
      <description>Save with one of our top michaels coupons for december 2021: Browse michaels store hours and sales, from the best deals on tech to the. Save on decorations, candles, crafts and .
  Craftaholics AnonymousÂ® | Colorful Mini Christmas Trees from www.craftaholicsanonymous.net  Winter, snowman, snow, christmas, holiday, santa, ornaments, clearance. Score major deals on craft supplies, art tools, artificial christmas trees, and holiday decorations at michaels&amp;#039; black friday sale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holiday Treats Recipes 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/holiday-treats-recipes-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/holiday-treats-recipes-2021/</guid>
      <description>Can substitute marshmallow creme instead of marshmallows. Sometimes you&amp;#039;re so hungry you could eat a horse! Transform your leftover turkey into tacos, potatoes into pancakes, pie into parfaits, and much more with these innovative (and healthy) recipes that will have you savoring your thanksgiving dinner throughout the long weekend.
  Red White and Blue Pretzel Bites - The Gunny Sack from www.thegunnysack.com  Sometimes you&amp;#039;re so hungry you could eat a horse!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multi Colored Garland 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/multi-colored-garland-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/multi-colored-garland-2021/</guid>
      <description>An easy way to make a simple colorful bracelet and show off your unique style! Cool colors are not overpowering and tend to recede in space. We may earn commission on some of the items you choose to buy.
  Patio Lights - Multicolor Satin Party Lights, 50 G50 E17 Bulbs Black Wire from cdn.christmaslightsetc.com  Looking at the guides available, though, you might start to t. We may earn commission on some of the items you choose to buy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grinch Food Ideas 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/grinch-food-ideas-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/grinch-food-ideas-2021/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to presenting that meal, most people just want their food without dealing with any kind of fanfare that complicates everything. A heterotroph is not capable of making its own food. Adults love this convenience food because it makes cooking that much simpler, and kids love the mildly terrorizing thrill of popping the can.
  String Cheese Snowman | Fun Family Crafts from funfamilycrafts.com  Your kidneys are powerful filtration systems that remove toxins from your blood to keep you healthy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dixie Stampede Christmas 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/dixie-stampede-christmas-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/dixie-stampede-christmas-2021/</guid>
      <description>Snow falls softly as the breathtaking scenes fill you with tidings of good cheer. I don&amp;#039;t want to wait for search results for dixie stampede christmas show 2021 too long, can you fix this? Nothing compares to the grand performances and holiday festivities of christmas at dolly parton’s stampede in branson, mo.
  Dolly Parton&amp;#039;s Dixie Stampede Dinner Attraction from dollyparton.com  On the page of dixie stampede christmas show 2021 search results, besides suggestions of events, popular searches are also provided in order to help users have more choice and keep up with the current trend of events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dog Tree Topper 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/dog-tree-topper-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/dog-tree-topper-2021/</guid>
      <description>Few things in life are more universally loved than dogs. There are a number of causes, including parasites, illness or eating something they shouldn’t have. Regardless of cause, here are a few remedies to get yo.
  Sonic the Hedgehog Movie Edible Cake Image Topper Circle | The Monkey Tree from www.monkeytree.co.nz  Finding the right dog can make a positive difference in a senior’s life. People easing into their golden years will enjoy th.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cute Ornament Ideas 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/cute-ornament-ideas-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/cute-ornament-ideas-2021/</guid>
      <description>If you ever need a dose of cuteness, then one surefire way to get it is by looking at pictures of baby animals. Work it for work—it takes only minutes in the morn. Japan&amp;#039;s envoy of cute, hello kitty, has just turned 35.
  Advanced Embroidery Designs - FSL Christmas Stocking Ornament from www.advanced-embroidery-designs.com  176 3 a place where i collect cute things. These are one dozen free christmas crochet ornament patterns to make your holiday a handmade success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mini Christmas Garland 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/mini-christmas-garland-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/mini-christmas-garland-2021/</guid>
      <description>Brian patrick flynn photo b. Marshall brain there are two different techn. In my second instructables project, i&amp;#039;ll be showing you show to make a mini christmas tree and wreath using an old artificial tree.
  Christmas Icicle Light - 150 Clear Icicle Lights - Green Wire from cdn.christmaslightsetc.com  The holiday experts at hgtv.com share fun tabletop kids&amp;#039; christmas tree decorating ideas. Small christmas trees and tabletop christmas trees are excellent mini alternatives if you are looking to add style to a smaller space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multicolor Curtain Lights 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/multicolor-curtain-lights-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/multicolor-curtain-lights-2021/</guid>
      <description>But they do not affect the opinions and recommendations of the authors. Depending on how comfortable you are with sewing, you can try penny weights, cha. Multicolored blinking led light sculpture:
  300 LED Curtain Fairy Lights 8 Modes USB String Hanging Wall Lights from i5.walmartimages.com  But they do not affect the opinions and recommendations of the authors. If your curtains don&amp;#039;t drape correctly, they might need some curtain weights at the bottom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowman Hat Craft 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/snowman-hat-craft-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/snowman-hat-craft-2021/</guid>
      <description>Also available are santa hats and snowman faces. Hello everyone,this is a quick tutorial on how to make this easy christmas ornament at your home. Connect the two brim pattern pieces where indicated on the pattern.
  Fun and Creative Winter Themed Crafts For Kids - Hative from hative.com  You can make this snowman hat ornament in just 5 minutes wi. Make a snowman scarf from patterned paper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fluffy White Garland 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/fluffy-white-garland-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/fluffy-white-garland-2021/</guid>
      <description>Uratot 6 pieces christmas white faux fur ribbon 59 x 1.9 inch shaggy faux fur fabric roll for crafts christmas tree garlands, christmas . Length of the single garland = approx 5 feet. The wedding garlands feature strings of miniature white fluffy decorations attached to 12ft of ribbon.
  33 Chic White Christmas Tree Decor Ideas - DigsDigs from www.digsdigs.com  1.8m white fluffy snow ball garland. The wedding garlands feature strings of miniature white fluffy decorations attached to 12ft of ribbon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Memory Ornament Diy 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/memory-ornament-diy-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/memory-ornament-diy-2021/</guid>
      <description>15/12/2014 · nothing is more lasting than cherished memories. Cut out your heart template. For this holiday i decided to create this wonderful photo memories ornament for a few cherished moments i.
  Floating Ornament | In memory of | Print then Cut | Cricut - YouTube from i.ytimg.com  Cut out your heart template. I used the large one for this tutorial. Think of something that happened this year or in years past, that has impacted you the most.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Popsicle Christmas Crafts 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/popsicle-christmas-crafts-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/popsicle-christmas-crafts-2021/</guid>
      <description>Easter is a special time of year when families get together to eat their favorite foods, and games like easter egg rolling and egg hunts are played by children. 814 5 great classy little projects to spice up your christmas or holiday season. From functional furniture to crafty home decor, you can use some clever cuts and tidy finishes to bring your design dreams to li.
  Craft Stick Photo Frame | Fun Family Crafts from funfamilycrafts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fresh Pine Garland 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/fresh-pine-garland-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/fresh-pine-garland-2021/</guid>
      <description>Snip pine stems, or purchase it fresh from a local retailer. Mix faux sprigs of cedar, pine, magnolia leaves, juniper, etc. How to make fresh christmas garland.
  DIY Friday: Decorating with Christmas Garlands from betterdecoratingbible.com  In with your fresh greenery. White pine roping and garland can be found by the overhead door of the barn next to . How to make fresh christmas garland. Shop for fresh christmas garlands in fresh christmas greenery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paper Tree Topper 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/paper-tree-topper-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/paper-tree-topper-2021/</guid>
      <description>It uplifts the spirits of people during the winter and carries the refreshing scents of pine cones and spruce. Here’s more information on the jobs that tree service businesses. Both tree service technicians and certified arborists perform work on trees.
  Wonderful DIY Colorful Woven Star Snowflake from cdn.wonderfuldiy.com  People have an innate curiosity about the natural world around them, and identifying a tree by its leaves can satisfy that curiosity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowman Socks Craft 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/snowman-socks-craft-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/snowman-socks-craft-2021/</guid>
      <description>Directions to make a tube sock snowman · as in the video, use a funnel to fill one white tube sock with rice. · use a piece of twine and tie it around the . Since i knew there was a possibility of my third graders using this .
  DIY Sock Snowman Easy &amp;amp; Quick Christmas Ornament from theseamanmom.com  · tie a knot at the top of the sock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Lights Cupcakes 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-lights-cupcakes-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-lights-cupcakes-2021/</guid>
      <description>Steer clear of bright combos of green, red, yellow and blue. Want to know how to make a christmas lights display to dazzle your neighbors? If you’ve got deep pockets and t.
  Rustic Wood Painted Christmas Ornaments - Domestically Speaking from www.domestically-speaking.com  Christmas is one of my favorite holidays, the snow, the lights, santa, gifts! Watch christmas lights, four ways from hgtv exterior decorating in an hour 03:35 exterior decorating in an hour 03:35 angelo surmelis shows how to decorate your home&amp;#039;s exterior in an hour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Net Fairy Lights 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/net-fairy-lights-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/net-fairy-lights-2021/</guid>
      <description>These warm white led fairy lights are suitable for both indoor and outdoor use. Design a four seasons wonderland in your yard with these bright net lights! Indoor outdoor 120/320leds blue net fairy lights.
  Best outdoor Christmas lights to give exteriors festive sparkle from ksassets.timeincuk.net  They can be hung from trees, wrapped in pillars, form curtains or anything else … Battery operated net fairy lights with timer!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Albertsons Christmas Dinner 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/albertsons-christmas-dinner-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/albertsons-christmas-dinner-2021/</guid>
      <description>To place an order, please call or visit your store and based on availability we will very happy to assist you. Well better late than never right?? Giant most stores are open from 8 am.
  Dr Pepper BBQ Sauce + Earn A $5 Fantastic Promo Code #AD Dazzling Daily from i0.wp.com  We’re committed to making your event a resounding success and are … Our dedicated team of albertsons catering and event professionals are here to help make your next event a huge success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Christmas Dinner 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/simple-christmas-dinner-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/simple-christmas-dinner-2021/</guid>
      <description>Many restaurants are open on christmas day and even offer special meals and deals to patrons. Our good housekeeping guide to the cheapest christmas dinner will help you do your christmas food shop for as little as £2.72 per head! Soups are an easy, affordable, nutritious staple to add to your repertoire of dinner ideas.
  55 Gorgeous Christmas Table Setting Ideas â Design Swan from img.designswan.com  Each recipe is perfect for creating a traditional mexican christmas dinner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowman Decoration Ideas 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/snowman-decoration-ideas-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/snowman-decoration-ideas-2021/</guid>
      <description>You can go with the usual look and body of a . They are perfect for decorating throughout the winter season. Have fun with the kids, we offer you some ideas on how to design a snowman.
  25 Creative Outdoor Valentine DÃ©cor Ideas - DigsDigs from www.digsdigs.com  Diy snowman decorations &amp;amp; crafts. Have fun with the kids, we offer you some ideas on how to design a snowman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Sewing Crafts 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-sewing-crafts-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-sewing-crafts-2021/</guid>
      <description>See the full tutorial here. 16/12/2019 · here are a few other christmas sewing projects and crafty ideas: Perfect for a toy or home decor, i love this stick reindeer!
  Tutorial: 5-minute fabric cookie gift bags, plus a recipe â Sewing from i0.wp.com  From advent calendars to tree … 28/11/2018 · today, i’ve rounded up more than twenty terrific christmas sewing projects to make. Simpler than my quilted tree skirt pattern, this free tree skirt pattern is beautiful too!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Countdown Projector 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-countdown-projector-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-countdown-projector-2021/</guid>
      <description>Count the days, hours, minutes, and even seconds to christmas with this countdown spotlight! Smartlights led projection countdown to christmas in blue light digital rare nib. Display will show the time until christmas based on the time just entered.
  Gemmy LED LIGHTSHOWÂ® COUNTDOWN PROJECTIONâ¢ Christmas Counts Down Up To from i.ebayimg.com  Counts down from up to 99 days; New disney magic holiday mickey mouse countdown to christmas projector gemmy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bucilla Ornament Kits 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/bucilla-ornament-kits-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/bucilla-ornament-kits-2021/</guid>
      <description>If you’re just starting out, answering that question can be tricky. First aid kits come in different sizes, for different purposes and the contents of a first aid kit may be adjusted for specific activities, according to the red cross. Consider packing a first aid kit to keep in your car, your home or your.
  Weekend Kits Blog: DIY Christmas Ornaments &amp;amp; Felt Stocking Kits! from 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowman Ornament Craft 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/snowman-ornament-craft-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/snowman-ornament-craft-2021/</guid>
      <description>Get in the christmas spirit by creating these homemade christmas ornament crafts with your kids. There is plenty of food to go around on thanksgiving, but there is always space for dessert, especially when yo. And if you are one of the few families that doesn’t have any, they’re cheap and plentiful in home supply stores.
  Dollar Store Snowflake Snowman - The Keeper of the Cheerios from www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter Themed Wreaths 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/winter-themed-wreaths-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/winter-themed-wreaths-2021/</guid>
      <description>Want to know how to make a christmas wreath this year? We may earn commission on some of the items you choose to buy. Hi, my name is kasi schlueter, i’m going to show you how to make a cute fall wreath to decorate your house.
  33 Ways to Use Snowflakes for Winter Home Decorating from decor4all.com  These themed cheese boards are perfect for the upcoming fall and winter holidays, including halloween, kwanzaa, thanksgiving, and hanukkah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Family Pj Photos 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/family-pj-photos-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/family-pj-photos-2021/</guid>
      <description>Every holiday season, ree drummond&amp;#039;s family poses for photos wearing the sweetest and silliest christmas pajamas around. We&amp;#039;ve been doing christmas photos together since . Complete the form above and email us a photo to .
  Wine Down Pajamas in Women&amp;#039;s Jersey Knit Blends | Pajamas for Women from www.pajamagram.com  This is our way of celebrating families this christmas. Every holiday season, ree drummond&amp;#039;s family poses for photos wearing the sweetest and silliest christmas pajamas around.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wooden Christmas Presents 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/wooden-christmas-presents-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/wooden-christmas-presents-2021/</guid>
      <description>Take the wooden clothes pins apart. Wooden clothespins are practically ubiquitous in the u.s. We earn a commission for products purchased through some links in this article.
  Wood Frame DIY Lighted Christmas Present from www.christmaslightsetc.com  Man has been using wood to bring comfort to his life from the earliest of times. Boat building can be a rewarding hobby for people with basic carpentry experience who enjoy working with their hands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michaels Lighted Garland 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/michaels-lighted-garland-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/michaels-lighted-garland-2021/</guid>
      <description>Halloween black pine wreath glass/plastic ornaments . Michaels haute decor lighted merry christmas wood blocks. I purchased 3 strings of pom pom garland from michael&amp;#039;s craft store for my string of lights.
  20+ Awesome Rustic Christmas Decorations from fluxdecor.com  My christmas tree for the michaels maker dream team challenge is here! For this month&amp;#039;s michaels makers . Lighted holiday frosted pine wreath. Lighted holiday frosted pine wreath.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Chocolate Candy 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-chocolate-candy-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-chocolate-candy-2021/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;#039;s nothing sweeter than candy for the holidays! We&amp;#039;ve compiled chocolate selections for the family to share at ﻿christmas time. Enjoy this with your loved ones.
  Lindt Truffles Teacher Appreciation Gift with Free Printable Gift Tag from www.skiptomylou.org  Looking for an easy holiday cupcake idea? This sugarplum recipe contains different varieties of dried fruit and nuts. This fudge is easy to make and very delicious. If you buy from a link, we may earn a commission.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wooden Snowman Ornaments 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/wooden-snowman-ornaments-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/wooden-snowman-ornaments-2021/</guid>
      <description>Then you can display it on the table so it will look simple but still stunning. Add to favorites pack of 12 wooden christmas tree decorations | … Fasten the wooden pins on a cup or tin can for easier painting.
  Pin on Wooden Signs from i.pinimg.com  Wooden snowmen ornament set of 2 myrainydayfinds 5 out of 5 stars (173) $ 5.00. Look for slices that range from 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Metal Door Wreaths 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/metal-door-wreaths-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/metal-door-wreaths-2021/</guid>
      <description>If you’re thinking about diying this pr. Metal doors are very commonly used as front doors, garage doors and even shed doors. Leaking doors make it tough to keep your home, automobile or rv safe from mold and damage caused by water.
  Sunflower Wreath, Housewarming Gift, Sunflowers Wreath, Sunflower Front from i.etsystatic.com  Your local home improvement stor. In addition to spreading cheer, wreat. Find out in this week&amp;#039;s episode of the today&amp;#039;s homeowner podcast!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Woodturning Christmas Ornaments 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/woodturning-christmas-ornaments-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/woodturning-christmas-ornaments-2021/</guid>
      <description>T&amp;#039;is the season to make your own holiday ornaments! Find wooden christmas decorations, hand made wooden ornament, christmas ornament, wood turning, christmas tree, christmas ornament, . Turned ornaments are not only a delight to make but are .
  how to turn christmas ornaments - Woodworking Talk - Woodworkers Forum from www.woodworkingtalk.com  Check out our wood turned christmas ornaments selection for the very best in unique or custom, handmade pieces from our ornaments &amp;amp; accents shops.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Reindeer Food 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-reindeer-food-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-reindeer-food-2021/</guid>
      <description>Consuming certain things creates more waste that your. And many of those waste products your kidneys filter out come from the foods you eat. Do brussel sprouts deserve to stay?
  DIY Reindeer Pictures, Photos, and Images for Facebook, Tumblr from www.lovethispic.com  Each superfood has different benefits, but they generally possess some combination of protein, vitamins, fibe. Sign up for the tasty newsletter today! Your kidneys are powerful filtration systems that remove toxins from your blood to keep you healthy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nutcracker Wreath Ideas 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/nutcracker-wreath-ideas-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/nutcracker-wreath-ideas-2021/</guid>
      <description>Inspired by mackenzie childs designs. It&amp;#039;s the first day of the 12 days of christmas ideas blog hop! Tons of beautiful, easy to recreate ideas are linked below, including the .
  61 best christmas door decorations images on Pinterest | Christmas door from i.pinimg.com  It&amp;#039;s the first day of the 12 days of christmas ideas blog hop! Harrington wreath pink christmas card birth announcement. Inspired by mackenzie childs designs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Window Fairy Lights 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/window-fairy-lights-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/window-fairy-lights-2021/</guid>
      <description>For christmas this year i decided to use a glass block, a pwm controller and some led fairy light strands to give my wife a colorful gift. 595 1 do you have random jars lying around your house? Bring a piece of nature indoors with this diy fairy light branch.
  40+ Best Old Window Outdoor Decor Ideas and Designs for 2021 from homebnc.com  If you buy through links on this page, we m.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rudolph Dog Costume 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/rudolph-dog-costume-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/rudolph-dog-costume-2021/</guid>
      <description>A good one will come with a vibrate or buzz function, as well as a wide range of stim levels. Reindeer dog costume, dog winter hat,dog ugly deer, crocheted dog accessories, puppy hat,dog beanie,dog clothes small ,pet christmas costume. 14/12/2021 · rudolph dog costume 😁why does my dog growl when i try to move her in bed?
  TROLL POPPY MASCOT MASCOTTE COSTUME - JS PARTY from english.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decorated Flocked Tree 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/decorated-flocked-tree-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/decorated-flocked-tree-2021/</guid>
      <description>However, where did this traditio. Both tree service technicians and certified arborists perform work on trees. A christmas tree adorned with twinkling lights and ornaments is an essential holiday decoration.
  Oh Flamingo Tree, Oh Flamingo Tree - Aunt Peaches from www.auntpeaches.com  As expected, everyone got creative. However, where did this traditio. A christmas tree adorned with twinkling lights and ornaments is an essential holiday decoration. It uplifts the spirits of people during the winter and carries the refreshing scents of pine cones and spruce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Led Xmas Lights 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/led-xmas-lights-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/led-xmas-lights-2021/</guid>
      <description>Business listings of led decorative lights, led christmas lights manufacturers, suppliers and exporters in surat, एलईडी डेकोरेटिव लाइट विक्रेता, सूरत, gujarat along with their contact details &amp;amp; address. Find here diwali decorative lights, christmas lights, christmas tree lights, suppliers, manufacturers, wholesalers, traders with diwali decorative lights … Find here led decorative lights, led christmas lights, led decoration lights suppliers, manufacturers, wholesalers, traders with led decorative lights …
  LED Christmas Lights - 70 5mm Warm White LED Icicle Lights from cdn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modern Xmas Decorations 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/modern-xmas-decorations-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/modern-xmas-decorations-2021/</guid>
      <description>Available in a wide variety of styles from the traditional and vintage to modern and unique, make your home stand out and excite friends and family, getting . Take a look through these 15 modern ideas that think outside of christmas&amp;#039; . You can go classic with a green tree, or put a modern .
  40 Amazing Outdoor Christmas Decorations To Get Inspired - Gardenoholic from i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homemade Gifts Easy 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/homemade-gifts-easy-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/homemade-gifts-easy-2021/</guid>
      <description>When you take a thoughtful gift and add customization, it shows extra care and makes it more meaningful. No matter if you’re celebrating a secret santa gift exchange during a holiday office party or if a staff member’s birthday is coming up, finding unique employee gifts makes these moments memorable. You can choose a useful gift or one to make them laugh out loud.
  60+ Creative Teabag Designs For Tea Lovers from cdn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holiday Family Pictures 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/holiday-family-pictures-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/holiday-family-pictures-2021/</guid>
      <description>In addition to matters out of your control, there are sev. We’ve come up with 12 fun crafts that kids of all ages can participate in. In addition, that light is controlled by a motion detector that&amp;#039;s not attached to the l.
  10 Unique DIY Christmas Decor Options - Resin Crafts from resincraftsblog.com  A child?s education should be a parent?s top priority. In theory, nothing sounds nicer or more wholesome than spending a few cozy days with family making holiday cookies, listening to seasonal tunes, and—of course—bonding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clay Ornament Ideas 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/clay-ornament-ideas-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/clay-ornament-ideas-2021/</guid>
      <description>This craft project requires few . Once you finish making your air dry clay or salt dough, lets explore some fun techniques to make christmas decorations that look fabulous in so . After a couple of minutes, the mixture .
  FALL AND HALLOWEEN CLAY POT IDEAS - The Keeper of the Cheerios from www.thekeeperofthecheerios.com  In a medium sized pot combine the cornstarch, baking soda, and water.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mccormick Cinnamon Ornaments 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/mccormick-cinnamon-ornaments-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/mccormick-cinnamon-ornaments-2021/</guid>
      <description>These handmade cinnamon ornaments are a great diy decoration for them to work . Shop for mccormick® ground cinnamon (2.37 oz) at ralphs. This time of year we make so many snickerdoodles and christmas ornaments with this cinnamon and the difference in taste and aroma between mccormick and .
  Some of These Things: Cinnamon Ornaments from 3.bp.blogspot.com  This time of year we make so many snickerdoodles and christmas ornaments with this cinnamon and the difference in taste and aroma between mccormick and .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cute Christmas Appetizers 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/cute-christmas-appetizers-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/cute-christmas-appetizers-2021/</guid>
      <description>· rosted parmesan garlic shrimp # . Stuffed jalapeños with gorgonzola and bacon ; Try these dip ideas · cheesy artichoke dip · curry hummus · cranberry pecan cheese ball · beet hummus · bacon wrapped .
  Christmas Cheer for Your Co-Workers | Pizzazzerie from pizzazzerie.com  Cranberry brie bites · 1 · cranberry brie bites ; French dip squares · 3 · french dip squares ; We&amp;#039;ve rounded some quick and easy holiday appetizers that take less than 30 minutes to make.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diy 2021 Ornament 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/diy-2021-ornament-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/diy-2021-ornament-2021/</guid>
      <description>Wind two pieces of yarn in different colors around a wood curtain ring. These projects are perfect for a rainy saturday afternoon, and many are easy enough for you to build with kids. Pick your favorite font and stencil it on to.
  Christmas crafts for kids - Making Christmas tree ornaments with pasta from www.12thblog.com  What’s halloween without halloween decorations? Create memories as you put together these diy christmas ornaments from hgtv magazine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grinch Themed Party 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/grinch-themed-party-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/grinch-themed-party-2021/</guid>
      <description>Find the perfect theme with. By bagnitsch in kids by bagnit. Every item on this page was chosen by a woman&amp;#039;s day editor.
  Novel Concept Designs - Grinch - Christmas - Birthday Party - Thank You from cdn.shopify.com  Throw a memorable party with a theme that works for any type of occasion. Rd.com holidays &amp;amp; observances christmas christmas parties may look a little different this year, thanks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chrismon Ornament Kits 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/chrismon-ornament-kits-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/chrismon-ornament-kits-2021/</guid>
      <description>A variety of supplies for making beautiful chrismon ornaments. 2mm, 3mm, 4mm, 5mm, 6mm. Styrofoam beaded christmas ornament kits, diy beaded christmas ornament kits, holiday beaded ornament kit, vintage beaded ornament kits, beaded satin ornament kits, satin beaded christmas ornament kits, beaded ornament kits to make, …
  102 Best Chrismons images | Christian symbols, Christmas ornaments from i.pinimg.com  5 out of 5 stars. 48 pieces wooden cardinal christmas ornaments … (346 results) price ($) any price.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yoda Tree Topper 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/yoda-tree-topper-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/yoda-tree-topper-2021/</guid>
      <description>Top your tree with this stellar angel every item on this page was chosen by a woman&amp;#039;s day editor. We researched the best christmas tree toppers, from angels to stars and snowflakes to bows. With help from these descriptions.
  Baby Yoda Christmas Tree Star Topper: Where to Buy and How to Use for from 1734811051.rsc.cdn77.org  You can have fun creating the angel the personality and style that you want using recycled materials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Popcorn Cranberry Garland 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/popcorn-cranberry-garland-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/popcorn-cranberry-garland-2021/</guid>
      <description>The popcorns and cranberries are enough to fill . A woman stringing popcorn and fresh cranberries to make a strand of garland. Push the needle through the center of a popcorn kernel, and pull it through to the end of the thread.
  Happy Kind of Life: Day 4 of Christmas Crafting: Popcorn Garland from 1.bp.blogspot.com  Package includes 9.2 feet old fashion christmas popcorn and cranberry garland string.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowman Craft Ideas 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/snowman-craft-ideas-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/snowman-craft-ideas-2021/</guid>
      <description>22/09/2020 · next, draw small circles, one below the other resembling the face and the body of the snowman. One snowman should rest on the fold line and the other opposite to the fold. Genius and super simple snowmen luminaries.
  25 DIY Snowman Craft Ideas and Tutorials for Kids from www.spongekids.com  16/12/2016 · break out the cotton ball! 07/12/2021 · kids art advent calendar. For older kids or keen crocheters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burlap Garland Ideas 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/burlap-garland-ideas-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/burlap-garland-ideas-2021/</guid>
      <description>There is something so satisfying about seeing something in the store or online, then making it for a . Check out these fun craft ideas below for fall or visit our entire crafts . If you build the embellishment separately, you can attach a large pin or .
  Top 21 The Most Spectacular &amp;amp; Unique DIY Christmas Tree Ideas from www.architectureartdesigns.com  Other embellishment ideas · use silk flowers in colors of the season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crayola Christmas Countdown 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/crayola-christmas-countdown-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/crayola-christmas-countdown-2021/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;#039;re very sorry, this item crayola christmas countdown advent calendar is out of stock. Each numbered door on the . Find quality entertainment products to add to your shopping list or order .
  12 Best Advent Calendars 2017 - Cool Advent Calendars With Chocolate &amp;amp; Toys from spyj82wkesvym5c49l0szbra-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com  Crayola art supplies &amp;amp; activities: Fun craft projects, gifts, and coloring activities to help kids count down to christmas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Children&amp;amp;#039;s Christmas Tree 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/children-039-s-christmas-tree-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/children-039-s-christmas-tree-2021/</guid>
      <description>Once upon a time, people thought they had to seal and dress tree wounds to help the damage heal and prevent disease. Both tree service technicians and certified arborists perform work on trees. A christmas tree adorned with twinkling lights and ornaments is an essential holiday decoration.
  Decorate an Outdoor Christmas Tree With Edible Ornaments for Wildlife from realfarmacy.com  With help from these descriptions. We may earn commission on some of the items you choose to buy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun Snowman Ideas 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/fun-snowman-ideas-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/fun-snowman-ideas-2021/</guid>
      <description>More diy snowman ideas from friends around the web ; The use of glitter really brings out the snowman&amp;#039;s appearance . Toy story fans will love the idea of a buzz lightyear snowman!
  19 Christmas Classroom Doors to Welcome the Holidays | Door decorations from i.pinimg.com  Makes a fun homemade gift too! The use of glitter really brings out the snowman&amp;#039;s appearance . Diy snowman/snowman making from thermocole ball/snowman making idea for /snowman craft learn how to make.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garland Over Fireplace 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/garland-over-fireplace-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/garland-over-fireplace-2021/</guid>
      <description>Easter and spring are full of bright and festive colors, so we decided to liven up our bric. If your garland didn’t come with lights, you’ll want to add them add this point. This is totally an “in progress” picture.
  Christmas fireplace garland â on the mantel or above? | Founterior from founterior.com  If your garland didn’t come with lights, you’ll want to add them add this point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7Th January Christmas 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/7th-january-christmas-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/7th-january-christmas-2021/</guid>
      <description>The seventh of january might not seem like a date that brings joy, but for orthodox christians, this is the peak of festivities as they . Christmas on january 7 is also known as old christmas day. Days were removed to make up for the difference with the julian .
  The Amsterdam light festival from www.trueamsterdam.com  Days were removed to make up for the difference with the julian .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Week 2021 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-week-2021-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-week-2021-2021/</guid>
      <description>Braun strowman trains to become a train from wrestlecrap.com wwe supershow holiday tour is coming to … Photos · the breathtaking images from smackdown, dec. Federal employees and most people in the nation will take friday, december 24th off from work to celebrate christmas day.
  This family&amp;#039;s love for &amp;#039;National Lampoon&amp;#039;s Christmas Vacation&amp;#039; is next from s.abcnews.com  2 days ago · ‘christmas comet’ leonard blazes through holiday skies the brightest comet of 2021, named leonard, is making its way across the sky just in time for the winter holiday season — and nasa says.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grinch Family Photos 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/grinch-family-photos-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/grinch-family-photos-2021/</guid>
      <description>If you buy from a link, we may earn a commission. We asked a professional photographer to critique the duchess&amp;#039; photography technique. We earn a commission for products purchased through some links in this article.
  Mr.Grinch Has Been Arrested from townsquare.media  You can use a special album to share images and video with your fellow family members, all courtesy of your icloud membership. Keeping your family photos organized is hard enough even if everything&amp;#039;s already digitized, but what do you do when you&amp;#039;re faced with decades of real photographs that aren&amp;#039;t organized at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aesthetic Christmas Bedroom 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/aesthetic-christmas-bedroom-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/aesthetic-christmas-bedroom-2021/</guid>
      <description>These design tips will help you when remodeling your bedroom to give it a modern touch. We ask a lot of ou. Get ready to transform your bedroom into the ultimate refug.
  33 Cute And Simple Shabby Chic Bedroom Decorating Ideas Â» EcstasyCoffee from i2.wp.com  No matter if you’re redecorating a child’s or a master bedroom, having design ideas are helpful. Discover just what you need to give your bedroom the right touch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Outdoor Tree Topper 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/outdoor-tree-topper-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/outdoor-tree-topper-2021/</guid>
      <description>Tree topper tree toppers 2021 tree topper ideas tree topper star tree topper holder tree topper bows tree topper angel tree topper star craft tree … 3.2 out of 5 stars8. And never has that spirit been so beautifully presented as it is by holiday magic at blue mountain.
  Predecorated Trees - 3&amp;#039; Royal Gold Battery Operated Table Top Potted Tree from cdn.christmaslightsetc.com  18/11/2021 · ad selection of furniture décor storage items and kitchen accessories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homemade Xmas Decorations 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/homemade-xmas-decorations-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/homemade-xmas-decorations-2021/</guid>
      <description>These easy homemade christmas decoration ideas will bring warmth and style into your home with ease. One particular pleasure of kids and grownups alike is, of course, the illustrious christmas tree. 35 diy christmas decorations for home, do it yourself easy crafts ;
  25+ Ideas To Decorate Your Home With Recycled Wood This Christmas from cdn.architecturendesign.net  · diy show stopping homemade christmas tree. 10 simple ideas for homemade christmas decorations that kids can do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minimalist Christmas Ornaments 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/minimalist-christmas-ornaments-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/minimalist-christmas-ornaments-2021/</guid>
      <description>Florist making a christmas wreath. Diy or purchase natural christmas ornaments for your minimalist christmas tree this year! Simple minimalist christmas decorations you can find or make on a budget including minimalist christmas trees, ornaments, mantles, garlands, .
  55 Minimalist Christmas DÃ©cor Ideas - DigsDigs from www.digsdigs.com  Accent the beauty of a tree with naturalistic ornaments that would typically be found on a tree: Simple minimalist christmas decorations you can find or make on a budget including minimalist christmas trees, ornaments, mantles, garlands, .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Olaf Door Decoration 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/olaf-door-decoration-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/olaf-door-decoration-2021/</guid>
      <description>Decorate your front door with a festive makeover this holiday. To make this fun olaf door decoration all you need is a few basic supplies you probably already have around the house. Here are 45 festive holiday classroom doors to get the creative juices flowing.
  &amp;quot;Don&amp;#039;t Feed The Reindeer&amp;quot; Classroom Door Decoration For Christmas from www.craftymorning.com  This frozen olaf door can be a creative project for the whole family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Outside Xmas Decorations 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/outside-xmas-decorations-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/outside-xmas-decorations-2021/</guid>
      <description>Buy outdoor christmas decorations from argos. Christmas front porch makeover | outdoor christmas decorations 2021 | christmas 2021 diy decor | christmas 2021 diy outdoor decorationstoday . Explore online for christmas decoration items, such as lights .
  26 Super Cool Outdoor DÃ©cor Ideas With Christmas Lights - DigsDigs from www.digsdigs.com  Order online today for fast home delivery. Explore online for christmas decoration items, such as lights .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Denny&amp;amp;#039;s Christmas Hours 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/denny-039-s-christmas-hours-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/denny-039-s-christmas-hours-2021/</guid>
      <description>Dennys also offers a turkey dinner and dressing pack. But before venturing out check … Everything hash browns onions cheddar cheese country gravy 389.
  Craig\&amp;#039;S Thanksgiving Dinner / Denny S Holiday Hours 2019 How To Order from imagesvc.meredithcorp.io  What are denny’s christmas eve hours? Call ahead to check the exact denny’s holiday hours of operation. Denny’s remains 24 hours open for its customers on the christmas day to offer delicious food.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Wreaths Pinterest 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-wreaths-pinterest-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-wreaths-pinterest-2021/</guid>
      <description>A gorgeous wreath is an easy way to get in the holiday spirit. Learn how to make holiday wreaths from classic holiday decorations . Here are 40 of the best christmas wreaths for a warm welcome.
  Beautiful Christmas Ladder Village - Crafty Morning from www.craftymorning.com  You&amp;#039;ll want to keep these pretty diy wreaths up all winter long. A gorgeous wreath is an easy way to get in the holiday spirit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Days To Xmas 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/days-to-xmas-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/days-to-xmas-2021/</guid>
      <description>Unlike memorial day, which is the day for honoring those who passed away while serving in the milit. They say laughter is the best medic. It&amp;#039;s anna&amp;#039;s eleventh birthday today.
  I will design easter and christmas flyers or posters for $20 - PixelClerks from pixelclerks.com  After all of the hustle and bustle leading up to christmas the last thing many people want to worry about is cooking on the big day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neutral Christmas Decor 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/neutral-christmas-decor-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/neutral-christmas-decor-2021/</guid>
      <description>But if traditional red and gree. Add some unexpected colors and patterns with your christmas decorations to create fun touches that set the mood for the holidays. Check out these inventive christmas decor ideas that won&amp;#039;t deplete your pocketbook.
  Christmas Foyer Table Decor | Christmas table centerpieces, Christmas from i.pinimg.com  Shop cheap and minimalist christmas decor. But if traditional red and gree. This is an instructable on how to make christmas decorations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garland Hanger Outdoor 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/garland-hanger-outdoor-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/garland-hanger-outdoor-2021/</guid>
      <description>If you want a christmas garland over your doorway, then using nails may not be the best method. This patented garland hanger allows you to hang garland around your front door without damaging your home with nails or screws. Home is where the heart is.
  Coat Hanger Christmas Tree - Free Craft Project from i2.wp.com  Learn how to hang outdoor christmas garland around your front door so your home will be looking beautiful and.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pier One Ornaments 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/pier-one-ornaments-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/pier-one-ornaments-2021/</guid>
      <description>Add to favorites li bien 2021 a happy halloween a pier 1 tradition libienornaments 5 out of 5 stars (442) star seller $ 32.00. Grab them while stocks last! Pier one top ornament, cloisonne top ornament, holly leaf top ornament, embossed gold green pier one, gold top ornament, new in box vintagechristmasetsy 5 out of 5 stars (542) $ 19.99.
  The Welcomed Guest: Gingerbread Tablescape from 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pink Christmas Outfit 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/pink-christmas-outfit-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/pink-christmas-outfit-2021/</guid>
      <description>Check out my stories for some of my top picks. From christmas dinner with the family to cocktails with coworkers, these cute and trendy looks will have you looking and feeling your best . It is made using a beautiful locally manufactured 100% .
  White Sweater Dress Picture Collection | DressedUpGirl.com from www.dressedupgirl.com  River island pink asymmetric tie neck midi dress. For the promotions of her upcoming release brahmastra, alia decked up in a glittery bomber jacket in shades of turquoise, blue and pink by .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Mantelpiece Decorations 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-mantelpiece-decorations-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-mantelpiece-decorations-2021/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;#039;s how to decorate for christmas with ornaments you&amp;#039;re not using. Festive styling experts reveal their tricks of the trade to help you bring a professional finish to your christmas decorating ideas. This is the simplest christmas decor, and looks great, whether it is in a window, or on your bathroom counter.
  10 Insanely Easy Christmas Light Bulb Decorations and Ornaments - DIY from www.diyncrafts.com  Decorate your home for christmas using glasses, ornaments, and other items that you already own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paper Snowflake Ideas 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/paper-snowflake-ideas-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/paper-snowflake-ideas-2021/</guid>
      <description>Registration on or use of this site constitutes acceptance of our terms of service. For your home office or small business use, you. Today i will be showing you how to make a simple and easy paper snowflake.
  DIY Easy Paper Cut Snowflake | iCreativeIdeas.com from www.icreativeideas.com  196 1 today i will be showing you how to make a simple and easy paper snowflake. Today i will be showing you how to make a simple and easy paper snowflake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whoville Mayor Costume 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/whoville-mayor-costume-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/whoville-mayor-costume-2021/</guid>
      <description>Some of these furry outfits are so impressive, . Costume and wardrobe department (30) · editorial department (12) . With christmas around the corner, these holiday crossover costumes are a super fun and festive idea.
  Mr. &amp;amp; Mrs. Mayor of Whoville | Seussical costumes, Christmas costumes from i.pinimg.com  With christmas around the corner, these holiday crossover costumes are a super fun and festive idea. It wouldn&amp;#039;t be whoville without our costume contest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inflatable Gingerbread Man 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/inflatable-gingerbread-man-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/inflatable-gingerbread-man-2021/</guid>
      <description>Tall 2.4m cute and smiling gingerbread man design, holding a striped candy cane · inner lights to illuminate for a cool atmosphere at night · mains powered, . It lights up with leds and stands out at night. Our gingerbread man inflatable is great for making a statement outside your home this christmas.
  Christmas Santa Animated Gingerbread Man In Cup Mug Cocoa Airblown from christmasyarddecor.info  Celebrate the season with an airblown inflatable gingerbread man!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Handmade Christmas Trees 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/handmade-christmas-trees-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/handmade-christmas-trees-2021/</guid>
      <description>Creating an organized &amp;amp; pretty, happy home!: Finish the decoration with rhinestones, sequins and beads. 12/12/2012 · paper punched christmas tree from rook no.
  12 Cutest And Easiest DIY Christmas Window DÃ©corations - Shelterness from i.shelterness.com  Gold topiary trees from positively splendid. Fabric canvas christmas trees from providence handmade. Blue i style | decorating, organizing &amp;amp; diy. Check out our christmas tree bronze selection for the very best in unique or custom handmade pieces from our shops.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Star Craft 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-star-craft-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-star-craft-2021/</guid>
      <description>Your kids can help make these simple star shapes by decorating them with red and green candies. Great classy little projects to spice up your christmas or holiday season. No matter how much distance you put between the past and the present, there always seems to be more than a few famous faces that resemble the iconic looks of the stars of yesteryear.
  150+ Homemade Toilet Paper Roll Crafts - Hative from hative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cinnamon Stick Ornaments 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/cinnamon-stick-ornaments-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/cinnamon-stick-ornaments-2021/</guid>
      <description>For one tree, cut eight pieces of ribbon around 6 inches in length. Glue this onto the back of the cinnamon stick. Take another cinnamon stick and line it up next to the the glued sticks, staggering it a little lower.
  30 Handmade Christmas Decorations with Cinnamon Sticks Adding Seasonal from www.lushome.com  Lay 4 pieces of ribbon on a flat surface, lined up evenly one on top of the other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hours Till Christmas 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/hours-till-christmas-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/hours-till-christmas-2021/</guid>
      <description>The cookie settings on this website are set to allow cookies to give you the best browsing experience possible. Christmas countdowns have been around for as long as we were celebrating christmas, thoguh these were mainly daily … How many days until christmas day?
  Bob&amp;#039;s Diner from eatatbobsdiner.com  How many weeks until christmas day? Our hours until christmas day clock will show you how long you have left till xmas day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Costco Christmas Dinner 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/costco-christmas-dinner-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/costco-christmas-dinner-2021/</guid>
      <description>Costco is partnering with rastelli&amp;#039;s to bring its members holiday meal delivery kits. Celebrate christmas with costco&amp;#039;s fantastic range of delicious christmas food this festive season. Christmas dinner | jon kempner photography | food photography · instagram.
  A SUPER FUN CHRISTMAS GAME - Happy Home Fairy from happyhomefairy.com  For a traditional italian dinner, costco&amp;#039;s italian sausage pasta is . Costco is partnering with rastelli&amp;#039;s to bring its members holiday meal delivery kits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Pajama Pictures 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-pajama-pictures-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-pajama-pictures-2021/</guid>
      <description>Select from 7113 premium christmas pajamas of the highest . Shopping for matching family christmas pajamas (or hanukkah or even everyday pjs)? Jessica simpson shares christmas pajama photo fail on instagram.
  38 Of The Cutest and Most Fun Family Photo Christmas Card Ideas from www.woohome.com  We did a family photoshoot in our christmas pajamas today and lets just say, it&amp;#039;s a small feat to get 4 generations of humans to .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Waterfall Lights 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-waterfall-lights-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-waterfall-lights-2021/</guid>
      <description>If you’ve got deep pockets and t. Want to know how to make a christmas lights display to dazzle your neighbors? With a bit of effort and a dose of inspiration,.
  Hometalk | Underwater Lighting in a Waterfall from cdn.hometalk.com  That can&amp;#039;t be missed during the holiday season. Symphony of lights festivities like the winter festival of lights in watkins regional park, one of the most popu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homemade Xmas Gifts 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/homemade-xmas-gifts-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/homemade-xmas-gifts-2021/</guid>
      <description>4,532 61 is a friend&amp;#039;s birthday coming up? Every item on this page was chosen by a woman&amp;#039;s day editor. Looking to up your quarantine gaming habits?
  Peppermint Hot Cocoa Gifts â Kristi Murphy | DIY Blog from static1.squarespace.com  Here&amp;#039;s where you can shop a variety of materials to create homemade christmas gifts. While we receive compensation when you click links to. Check out these awesome post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making Christmas Tree 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/making-christmas-tree-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/making-christmas-tree-2021/</guid>
      <description>232 1 2 this design is a christmas tree made in a 3d printer.this tree is my best design in the 3d printer. It uplifts the spirits of people during the winter and carries the refreshing scents of pine cones and spruce. Learn more about the various types of cypress trees that grow in the u.s.
  Illuminated Garden: 8 Foot White Birch Tree - 240 Warm White LED&amp;#039;S from www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter Wonderland Outfits 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/winter-wonderland-outfits-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/winter-wonderland-outfits-2021/</guid>
      <description>The vibe this season is cozy luxe. Winter shop · black soft belted knitted jumper dress · prettylittlething orange chunky new season tab beanie · black vinyl contrast curly faux fur longline belted . Arrives by thu, dec 30 buy make nancy fancy winter wonderland outfit at walmart.com.
  15 Latest Winter Themed Wonderland Makeup Ideas &amp;amp; Trends 2016 | Modern from modernfashionblog.com  All of these garments blend together effortlessly to create a striking outfit ready for you to wear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preschool Ornament Crafts 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/preschool-ornament-crafts-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/preschool-ornament-crafts-2021/</guid>
      <description>Festive and simple kids&amp;#039; christmas ornaments trees. Preschool christmas ornaments templates, preschool christmas ornament crafts, kindergarten christmas ornaments to make, preschool christmas ornaments with pictures, preschool christmas tree ornaments, easy preschool christmas ornaments … Make this smiley snowflake ornament from white craft foam (or buy already cut out snowflakes) and google eyes.
  No-Sew Fabric Ornaments | Fun Family Crafts from funfamilycrafts.com  These salt dough santa handprint ornaments are great christmas keepsakes to use year after year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Entree Ideas 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-entree-ideas-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-entree-ideas-2021/</guid>
      <description>65 easy christmas dinner ideas to make the feast unforgettable ; Baked brie bites · 2. Beef tenderloin with roasted cauliflower salad · 1 · beef tenderloin with roasted .
  Get Inspired With 10 Cheerful Christmas Outdoor Decorations from cdn.homesthetics.net  Looking for christmas dinner ideas? · baked ham with pineapple · peppery roast beef · green bean bundles · duck with orange hazelnut stuffing · beef .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Store Ornaments 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/disney-store-ornaments-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/disney-store-ornaments-2021/</guid>
      <description>Save money without skimping on style with adorable ornaments you can make with toolbox treasures. Finding the best deals means saving money on gas, too. Whether you’re a deal hunter or you love finding interesting products, the dollar store makes saving a few bucks easier for everyone.
  2015 A World Within Miniature Hallmark Keepsake Ornament - Hooked on from www.hookedonhallmark.com  When you’re moving to a new area, locating department stores can be a priority, especially when you need curtains, bathroom accessories or picture frames.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schlumbergera Christmas Cactus 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/schlumbergera-christmas-cactus-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/schlumbergera-christmas-cactus-2021/</guid>
      <description>This cactus is named for the seasons that it typically blooms in: Learn how to grow yours in our . We have all seen them or owned one or two.
  Thanksgiving cactus â Biology Teaching Greenhouse from sites.berry.edu  Zygocactus schlumbergera &amp;#039;pink pearl&amp;#039; christmas cactus (pink) plant only : Technically several species under the genus schlumbergera . We have all seen them or owned one or two.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowman Door Wreath 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/snowman-door-wreath-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/snowman-door-wreath-2021/</guid>
      <description>A security door helps make your home a safer place, and you can find one that matches the decor of your home. They don’t just limit weather damage and enhance energy efficiency; From simple to creative, there&amp;#039;s a wreath here you&amp;#039;ll love.
  37 Beautiful Christmas Front Door Decor Ideas | Interior God from interiorgod.com  Using supplies most people have in their house. This wreath is a simple project that takes no more than a half an hour to complete.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Family Pajama Photoshoot 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/family-pajama-photoshoot-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/family-pajama-photoshoot-2021/</guid>
      <description>Petite plume evergreen pajama sets · carter&amp;#039;s family matching holiday pjs · old navy matching family hanukkah pajamas · tea collection goodnight . I wanted pajama photos of my kids in the back of the truck, . When it&amp;#039;s time for family photos around the christmas tree or another special occasion, let your pet join in for a complete portrait of your .
  Family Jammies with Pets | Lazy One â LazyOne from cdn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frozen Christmas Tree 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/frozen-christmas-tree-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/frozen-christmas-tree-2021/</guid>
      <description>Native cypress trees are evergreen, coniferous trees that, in the u.s., primarily grow in the west and southeast. Matt bliss rediscovered his grandfather&amp;#039;s playful designs from the &amp;#039;60s, and decided to share them with the world to revisit this article, visit my profile, then view saved stories. This design is a christmas tree made in a 3d printer.this tree is my best design in the 3d printer.
  32 Amazing Red And Gold Christmas DÃ©cor Ideas | DigsDigs from www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Fabric Wreath 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-fabric-wreath-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-fabric-wreath-2021/</guid>
      <description>The wreath was meant to represent the crown of thorns worn on the cross, with the red berries meant to be christ&amp;#039;s blood. My rag wreath fabric is remnants from christmas projects and dresses that i have made for my daughter and self. This wreath will create a comfortable atmosphere for .
  Christmas Wreath, Christmas Buffalo Plaid Wreath, Rustic Christmas from i.etsystatic.com  Diy christmas rag wreath · 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holiday Dessert Ideas 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/holiday-dessert-ideas-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/holiday-dessert-ideas-2021/</guid>
      <description>The best most comforting fall casserole recipes. 25/10/2019 · the flavors of gingerbread, salted caramel filling, and pumpkin cream cheese frosting marry to become the ultimate fall and holiday poke cake. Creamy cheesecakes, decadent pies, moist cakes and mouthwatering cookies are among our best holiday dessert recipes.
  Rustic Cuteness: 40 Thanksgiving Wedding Ideas - Weddingomania from i.weddingomania.com  Type keyword (s) to search. Creamy cheesecakes, decadent pies, moist cakes and mouthwatering cookies are among our best holiday dessert recipes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kids Tree Topper 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/kids-tree-topper-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/kids-tree-topper-2021/</guid>
      <description>This will be a tree topper for a nightmare before christmas theme. People have an innate curiosity about the natural world around them, and identifying a tree by its leaves can satisfy that curiosity. From a tiny seed can gro.
  Mini Christmas Tree Ideas | HGTV from hgtvhome.sndimg.com  Browse ideas for creative ways to craft a christmas tree. Family trees help children learn about their ancestry and identity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Christmas Treats 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/simple-christmas-treats-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/simple-christmas-treats-2021/</guid>
      <description>Looking for the fastest way to remove warts? With just a few common ingredients and a microwave you can make this simple but delicious gift. We earn a commission for products purchased through some links i.
  Tolle GeschenkanhÃ¤nger - DIY Geschenke ideen | Christmas gift tags diy from i.pinimg.com  Part of the reason stems from the fact that scientists aren’t able to pinpoint precisely what causes hangovers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Popsicle Stick Decorations 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/popsicle-stick-decorations-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/popsicle-stick-decorations-2021/</guid>
      <description>Turn popsicle sticks into christmas characters, like santa, rudolph, and a snowman with this easy craft for kids. Your kids will have so much fun decorating their popsicle stick skis with this easy ornament craft. Use colorful craft sticks to make snowflake decorations for your christmas tree with your kids.
  Grimm&amp;#039;s Wooden Toys | Leonardo Sticks (Da Vinci&amp;#039;s Bridge) from thewoodenwagon.com  Jumbo craft stick angels — craftbits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Light Up Santa 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/light-up-santa-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/light-up-santa-2021/</guid>
      <description>The belhelvie community are “appalled and saddened” by the theft. 4.2 out of 5 stars. Price and other details may vary based on product size and color.
  Shamrock Rose Aussies - ï»¿ï»¿ï»¿ Welcome to Shamrock Rose Aussies!! :) We from shamrockroseaussies.com  A light up, waving santa has been stolen from a charity display in aberdeenshire. Set to take place on nov. If you spot our light it up pulaski county santa, take a picture with him, and share it on facebook or … Set to take place on nov.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Red Christmas Cactus 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/red-christmas-cactus-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/red-christmas-cactus-2021/</guid>
      <description>Today, the restaurant remains one of the most beloved seafood chain eateries in the united states and around the world, with just under 750 locati. Ups does not use color codes for its shipping options, but next day air is tough to miss with the bright red color found on the envelope or package. Red meats are all meats that tend to be red when they are raw, but some red meats coul.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jingle Bells Decorations 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/jingle-bells-decorations-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/jingle-bells-decorations-2021/</guid>
      <description>Christmas bells and christmas high resolution . Instead of just using one bell, why not opt for two? Beautiful and cute christmas jingle bell design, ideal to decor christmas tree to light up festive atmosphere.
  51 Ideas To Use Jingle Bells In Christmas DÃ©cor - DigsDigs from www.digsdigs.com  Most items can be purchased at your local dollar or craft store inexpensively and they&amp;#039;re fun . Instead of just using one bell, why not opt for two?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheap Christmas Garland 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/cheap-christmas-garland-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/cheap-christmas-garland-2021/</guid>
      <description>One of the more versatile types of . Shop for christmas garlands in christmas wreaths &amp;amp; garlands. Great deals, cashbacks, discount offers &amp;amp; fast delivery option with millions of products to explore.
  Just Blenda: Christmas Centerpiece from 4.bp.blogspot.com  Holiday garland is one of the most versatile christmas decorations out there. Find artificial christmas garland at lowe&amp;#039;s today. Shop for christmas garlands in christmas wreaths &amp;amp; garlands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grandinroad Christmas 2021 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/grandinroad-christmas-2021-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/grandinroad-christmas-2021-2021/</guid>
      <description>Choose from solids, stripes, dots, and more, all with coordinating bows. Lets get this party started. In this case, they are colorful, decorative gifts, crafted of durable polyresin and suited for display indoors or out.
  Christmas Porch Decorations: 15 Holly Jolly Looks - Grandin Road Blog from i.pinimg.com  Choose from solids, stripes, dots, and more, all with coordinating bows. Save this post to read later. Season after season, gifts that continue to give holiday cheer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nativity Door Cover 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/nativity-door-cover-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/nativity-door-cover-2021/</guid>
      <description>The simple answer is “when it is ajar.” the riddle may seem straightforward, but it has a few complex details worth exploring. After you’ve selected a replacement that fits your needs, you can choose between doing the screen door. You need to make sure that you choose an opener you can rely on when you need it most for safety and convenience reasons.
  Christmas Nativity Scene Single Garage Door Cover Full Color Door from i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lighted Reindeer Costco 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/lighted-reindeer-costco-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/lighted-reindeer-costco-2021/</guid>
      <description>Costco 3pc led deer family price: 656 warm white led&amp;#039;s total wattage: Costco has already started putting out some of its big holiday items,.
  the Costco Connoisseur: September 2014 from 1.bp.blogspot.com  Lighted led deer family, set of 3. Buy reindeer family lifestyle image at costco.co.uk. Inventory and pricing may vary at your warehouse location and are subject . 656 warm white led&amp;#039;s total wattage: Costco has already started putting out some of its big holiday items,.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monday Before Christmas 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/monday-before-christmas-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/monday-before-christmas-2021/</guid>
      <description>The difficulty of hedging, the risks of option writing, and frozen websites. These four tips can help you feel a lot better next monday. Useless users, hapless bosses, clueless vendors and adventures in the it trenches.
  UPS will charge more for Christmas shipments from i2.cdn.turner.com  Useless users, hapless bosses, clueless vendors and adventures in the it trenches. I just studied 300b ad impressions, 9b clicks, 400m app installs, and $1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homemade Wood Ornaments 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/homemade-wood-ornaments-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/homemade-wood-ornaments-2021/</guid>
      <description>Plus, get our tips for displaying the christmas ornaments on your holiday tree. Homemade carbide wood lathe tool: Homes often have at least a few types of molding, usually along baseboards or around windows and doors.
  30 Beautiful Elegant Wood Slices for Chasing for Chrismas Decorating from i.pinimg.com  By sld7531 in woodworking by mercurska in woodworking by acuriouscreator in tools by ollaris in woodworking by matt makes in reuse by mikeasaurus in woodworkin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy Christmas Diy 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/easy-christmas-diy-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/easy-christmas-diy-2021/</guid>
      <description>If this describes you, you. Everyone loves a great handmade present, especially when it’s clear how much time, effort and love yo. Every year, it’s fun to garnish your home with winter greenery and holiday decorations, but this year — one that’s seen us all spending much more time around the house — it feels particularly exciting to freshen things up.
  40 Comfy Rustic Outdoor Christmas DÃ©cor Ideas | DigsDigs from www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fairy Light Garland 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/fairy-light-garland-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/fairy-light-garland-2021/</guid>
      <description>Christmas color lights isolated on white background. Bright colored garland lights decoration. Check out our fairy lights garland selection for the very best in unique or custom, handmade pieces from our craft supplies &amp;amp; tools shops.
  50cm Eucalyptus &amp;amp; Laurel Christmas Wreath | Lights4fun.co.uk from cdn.shopify.com  Buy 12m 54 led outdoor string lights led garland string fairy light christmas light holiday wedding party (blue) online at a discounted price from .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orange Slice Ornaments 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/orange-slice-ornaments-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/orange-slice-ornaments-2021/</guid>
      <description>(since the thickness of the slices may vary along . Holiday decorations from the kitchen: · secure them to a balsam wreath for a pop of color.
  Smeg Kettle &amp;amp; 2 Slice Toaster Set, Pastel Green | Leekes from www.leekes.co.uk  Blown glass orange segment slice christmas tree ornament decoration or bauble. Using a sharp knife, slice oranges thinly. · add them to garland for your mantle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michaels Christmas Crafts 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/michaels-christmas-crafts-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/michaels-christmas-crafts-2021/</guid>
      <description>We may earn commission on some of the items you choose to buy. We earn a commission for products purchased through some links in this article. While children may enjoy doing crafts, being able to eat your masterpiece once you have finished it makes it that much more fun.
  Garage Light Christmas Wreaths | Decorating with christmas lights from i.pinimg.com  You can make a game of these crafts by counting down five minutes and seeing if you can get each item made well within the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xmas Meal Ideas 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/xmas-meal-ideas-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/xmas-meal-ideas-2021/</guid>
      <description>The word “breakfast” comes from the action of “breaking the fast” that occurs overnight after your last meal of the day and continues until you eat the next morning. The variety of meal delivery services has taken off in recent years. Eating healthy can be hard when balancing everything in your life.
  32 Adorable Christmas Bedroom DÃ©cor Ideas | DigsDigs from www.digsdigs.com  Every time you decide what to eat, you either increase or decrease your chance of having a heart attack or stroke.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Christmas Theme 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/disney-christmas-theme-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/disney-christmas-theme-2021/</guid>
      <description>Disney world boasts magic brought to life at its theme parks and resorts. 07/07/2021 · white christmas disney 2021. With four gigantic theme parks, disney world can be overwhelming.
  50 Christmas HD Wallpapers For Iphone â The WoW Style from thewowstyle.com  05/11/2020 · this means it’s time to start decorating your home and bring that disney inspired theme inside. 26/10/2018 · fantastic disney theme christmas tree decoration idea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reindeer Feet Craft 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/reindeer-feet-craft-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/reindeer-feet-craft-2021/</guid>
      <description>(affiliate links included for your convenience!) welcome to day 4 of our holiday print art series with fsdpt! Reindeer handprint and footprint craft. Glue your foot print onto a piece of construction paper.
  Hand &amp;amp; Footprint Bats | Fun Family Crafts from funfamilycrafts.com  · have them place both hands on the paper and space them a little bit . Handprint reindeer christmas ornament · 1. Have your child spread his/ .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy Xmas Desserts 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/easy-xmas-desserts-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/easy-xmas-desserts-2021/</guid>
      <description>99 best easy christmas desserts to deck out your holiday treats table ; 3 · pecan caramel clusters ; 12 quick and easy christmas desserts ;
  40 Oh So Cute Christmas Treats and Desserts â Random Talks from randomtalks.snydle.com  Reindeer and tree cookies · 3 of 95. Eggnog cake · 3 of 85. Chocolate covered marshmallow reindeer yellow bliss road ; Christmas is the time to pull out all the stops when it comes to cooking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Trifle Dessert 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-trifle-dessert-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-trifle-dessert-2021/</guid>
      <description>Italians know how to do christmas. 23 trifle recipes for christmas and beyond ; This traditional christmas dessert, layered with fresh strawberry and raspberry jelly, creamy mascarpone custard and sherry soaked .
  Christmas Trifle from assets.marthastewart.com  Ingredients · 1 can (8 ounces) crushed pineapple · 3 medium firm bananas, sliced · 1 jar (10 ounces) red maraschino cherries · 1 jar (6 ounces) green maraschino .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cricut Christmas Tree 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/cricut-christmas-tree-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/cricut-christmas-tree-2021/</guid>
      <description>To revisit this article, select my account, then view save. It’s nothing against real trees; And from a cozy afternoon spent hanging ornaments to a christmas morning brimming with presents, so much of the holiday season revolves around the tree.
  Cone Christmas Tree Ideas | Crafting in the Rain from 4.bp.blogspot.com  In addition, many people use trees for landscaping, so it’s beneficial to know what species to look for wh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glitter Diy Ornaments 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/glitter-diy-ornaments-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/glitter-diy-ornaments-2021/</guid>
      <description>First, you’ll need to grab your supplies. Shatterproof, clear bauble ornaments (you can usually find these at most craft stores during the holiday season.) emphasis on the shatterproof, because you already know. Any glitter will do, but i think that fine glitter holds better.
  DIY Ideas: Make Christmas Ornaments at Home - Pretty Designs from www.prettydesigns.com  Any glitter will do, but i think that fine glitter holds better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coffee Filter Snowman 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/coffee-filter-snowman-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/coffee-filter-snowman-2021/</guid>
      <description>In this ible i will show you 11 unique ways to use coffee filters! We may earn commission on some of the items you choose to buy. Since i&amp;#039;m already on my second bulk box of popsicles this spring, i&amp;#039;ve been looking for a.
  30 Crafty Repurposing Ideas For Empty Coffee Containers - DIY &amp;amp; Crafts from cdn.diyncrafts.com  For a really great cup, understanding which filter to choose and how it works is essential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Fairy Lights 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/smart-fairy-lights-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/smart-fairy-lights-2021/</guid>
      <description>Work with alexa, google assistant. Decorative fairy lights are no more just an . Nowadays, there are various other options to light up your house apart from the regular lamps, lighting, and bulbs.
  Butterfly Fairy Lights - Smart Kids Toys from www.sktoys.com  Work with alexa, google assistant. Nowadays, there are various other options to light up your house apart from the regular lamps, lighting, and bulbs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walmart Christmas Suits 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/walmart-christmas-suits-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/walmart-christmas-suits-2021/</guid>
      <description>Six functional and fun styles that look great and stay put. How will it enhance your super powers?let&amp;#039;s find out! A jumpsuit tape black paint brush water alpha template black permanent marker pl.
  Christmas shower curtain Snowman Family Scarf | bath-supplies.store from www.bath-supplies.store  A jumpsuit tape black paint brush water alpha template black permanent marker pl. The birthday suit franchise information from entrepreneur.com signing out of account, standby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clothespin Reindeer Craft 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/clothespin-reindeer-craft-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/clothespin-reindeer-craft-2021/</guid>
      <description>When the glue is dry, cut antlers from brown felt. Glue the antlers to the reindeer’s head. 05/12/2019 · instructions using a black gel pen and a ruler, draw a straight line on the bottom of the clothespin.
  The Crafty Crystal: 12 Days of Christmas Crafts #2: Clothespin Reindeer from 4.bp.blogspot.com  Cut a small tail from the felt. 06/12/2017 · how to make the clothespin reindeer craft clothespins brown paint paint brush black marker brown construction paper scissors glue red pom pom yarn 20/10/2018 · reindeer clothespin ornament directions 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preschool Christmas Snacks 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/preschool-christmas-snacks-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/preschool-christmas-snacks-2021/</guid>
      <description>Snacks for hannukah, christmas, and three king&amp;#039;s day. Christmas tree and santa hat cupcakes · 4. 38 easy kids&amp;#039; christmas treats they&amp;#039;ll love · 2.
  8 Healthy Halloween Snacks for Kids! - Spend With Pennies from www.spendwithpennies.com  Bagel ornament snack (via fork and beans) ; Banana snowmen from one handed cooks ; Candy cane cake · 8. Healthy christmas treat ideas · babybel cheese (wrap to look like santa) · fruit (kebabs or cups) · bananas · pancakes (fun shapes with cookie .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Which Day Christmas 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/which-day-christmas-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/which-day-christmas-2021/</guid>
      <description>Veteran’s day is an important observance in the united states, set aside for honoring and remembering men and women who have served in the armed forces. Godparents day, sometimes called godparents&amp;#039; sunday, takes place on the first sunday in june every year. After all of the hustle and bustle leading up to christmas the last thing many people want to worry about is cooking on the big day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quilling Christmas Tree 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/quilling-christmas-tree-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/quilling-christmas-tree-2021/</guid>
      <description>It’s nothing against real trees; Sure, a freshly cut christmas tree smells great — for a few weeks while you’re also dealing with the high cost, the hauling home, the dog drinking its water and the eventual crispy fire hazard it becomes. Native cypress trees are evergreen, coniferous trees that, in the u.s., primarily grow in the west and southeast.
  quilling art: female characters in the wonderful paper art - crafts from craft-craft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Trees Aus 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-trees-aus-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-trees-aus-2021/</guid>
      <description>A christmas tree topper is often the last item placed on the christmas tree, helping to complete the festive look. The holiday experts at hgtv.com share fun tabletop kids&amp;#039; christmas tree decorating ideas. One smells great, but the other comes predecorated—and both can pollute.
  Easy DIY Pallet Christmas Tree Ideas To Amaze Everyone With Your Creativity from mykarmastream.com  We may earn commission from links on this page, but we only recommend products we back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eiffel Tower Ornament 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/eiffel-tower-ornament-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/eiffel-tower-ornament-2021/</guid>
      <description>Celebrate the holiday season or dress up your bastille day fête with our eiffel tower ornament. Glass paris eiffel tower christmas ornament, 5 1/8 tall, by merck family&amp;#039;s old world christmas. Crafted from acrylic coated in pastel pink .
  30 Fabulous Stay In the Vase Cemetery Flowers | Decorative vase Ideas from www.literaryhealingarts.com  Arrives by thu, jan 6 buy home metal paris eiffel tower model ornament collection bronze tone 8cm height for christmas at walmart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traditional Christmas Meal 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/traditional-christmas-meal-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/traditional-christmas-meal-2021/</guid>
      <description>The holidays just aren&amp;#039;t the holidays without a feast full of beautiful and delicious recipes to share. To choose the best food processo. The meals are delivered to your door, ready to heat up.
  Christmas Dinner â The Norwegian Way | Norwegian Arts from norwegianarts.org.uk  The word “breakfast” comes from the action of “breaking the fast” that occurs overnight after your last meal of the day and continues until you eat the next morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Costco Christmas Chocolates 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/costco-christmas-chocolates-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/costco-christmas-chocolates-2021/</guid>
      <description>The ghirardelli chocolate gift tower by wine country gift baskets. Find dark or milk chocolate, chocolate covered fruit, chocolate covered nuts, gourmet chocolate &amp;amp; more. By costco west 3 months ago .
  Ferrero Rocher Hazelnut Chocolates from costcocouple.com  From christmas trees to tasty holiday foods, costco&amp;#039;s seasonal. Shop costco.com for a large selection of chocolates. By costco west 3 months ago . Find dark or milk chocolate, chocolate covered fruit, chocolate covered nuts, gourmet chocolate &amp;amp; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holiday Recipe Ideas 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/holiday-recipe-ideas-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/holiday-recipe-ideas-2021/</guid>
      <description>As a diabetic, it’s important to make sure you eat healthy meals that don’t cause your blood sugar to spike. These are our favorite dishes from the kitchens that came before us. Some of the best holiday recipes have long family histories.
  Double Stacked Oreo Cake Video | Recipe in 2020 | Oreo cake recipes from i.pinimg.com  Find your favorite and dig in. The mixture of fruits and nuts helps make it a tasty treat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Tree Ornaments 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/disney-tree-ornaments-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/disney-tree-ornaments-2021/</guid>
      <description>If you’re trying to create a tropical oasis, you’ll definitely need a palm tree or two. We may earn commission from links on this page, but we only recommend products we back. A christmas tree adorned with twinkling lights and ornaments is an essential holiday decoration.
  10 Makit bakit Make It Bake It CHRISTMAS ORNAMENT Kit Santa Tree from i.pinimg.com  Here’s more information on the jobs that tree service businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pink Santa Dress 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/pink-santa-dress-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/pink-santa-dress-2021/</guid>
      <description>Pink santa claus with red trim. Discover pink santa claus on us $0.01. Maternity pink santa baby christmas sweatshirt.
   from mizzfit.com  Pink santa claus tutu romper santa tutu dress for girls. Pink santa claus with red trim. Buy pink and violet velvet santa dress with purse : Buy pink and violet velvet santa dress with purse : Christmas tutu holiday dress for santa babies. Pink sequin santa dress christmas dog &amp;amp; cat costume.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Countdown Craft 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-countdown-craft-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-countdown-craft-2021/</guid>
      <description>Doing crafts with your kids can help develop their coordination, improve visual processing abilities, hone fine motor skills in the smallest kids, and allow children of all ages to express themselv. Thanks to all the creative people who’ve made it a relatively simple affair to make a craft at home and you needn’t spend excessi. Great classy little projects to spice up your christmas or holiday season.
  150+ Homemade Toilet Paper Roll Crafts - Hative from hative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowman Eyes Ideas 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/snowman-eyes-ideas-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/snowman-eyes-ideas-2021/</guid>
      <description>What do you do when you have a problem w. Are people always telling you that you look tired? Moreover, the spasms may vary in strength and speed, but they most commonly occur aro.
  15+ Snowman Christmas Tree DIY Decorations and Ideas | Guide Patterns from www.guidepatterns.com  They also come with a host of varying symptoms. You might wonder what the reason might be. It can be hard to concentrate when your eyes are watering constantly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Holiday Treats 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/sweet-holiday-treats-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/sweet-holiday-treats-2021/</guid>
      <description>We may earn commission on some o. Each one is carb controlled but sweet and decadent enough to leave you fully satisfied. Gail also shares a few sweet holiday treats:
  Shamrock Rose Aussies - ï»¿ï»¿ï»¿ Welcome to Shamrock Rose Aussies!! :) We from shamrockroseaussies.com  These are all notable for their wild color combinations, attention to detail, and/or simplicity, but are all collected here for their ability to send one on a sugar ru.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Candy Cane Desserts 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/candy-cane-desserts-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/candy-cane-desserts-2021/</guid>
      <description>Assorted colors four days of. Kids will love creating these reindeer ornaments using m. If the dough of one color is shaped first, the little rolls become to dry to twist.
  Super-Cute Treats That Will Be The Highlight Of Your Christmas Party from i.pinimg.com  This is a simple, festive and tasty peppermint fudge. Assorted flavors food color paste ? If the dough of one color is shaped first, the little rolls become to dry to twist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starbucks Christmas Day 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/starbucks-christmas-day-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/starbucks-christmas-day-2021/</guid>
      <description>The word “breakfast” comes from the action of “breaking the fast” that occurs overnight after your last meal of the day and continues until you eat the next morning. Veteran’s day is an important observance in the united states, set aside for honoring and remembering men and women who have served in the armed forces. They say laughter is the best medic.
  Build-A-Bear Is Selling Nightmare Before Christmas Bears And They&amp;#039;re from cdn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Gifts Drawing 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-gifts-drawing-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/christmas-gifts-drawing-2021/</guid>
      <description>We earn a commission for products purchased through some links i. Inspiration is at hand with this christmas gift guide for home lovers, gardeners, cooks, children and gadget lovers. What better way is there to perk up.
  Wonderful Victorian Santa Image - The Graphics Fairy from thegraphicsfairy.com  Gift giving is a happy event, but it might be especially tricky when the etiquette and expectations of the professional world apply.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clothespin Christmas Crafts 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/clothespin-christmas-crafts-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/clothespin-christmas-crafts-2021/</guid>
      <description>And if you are one of the few families that doesn’t have any, they’re cheap and plentiful in home supply stores. While children may enjoy doing crafts, being able to eat your masterpiece once you have finished it makes it that much more fun. 814 5 great classy little projects to spice up your christmas or holiday season.
  25 Awesome DIY Christmas Decorating Ideas and Tutorials 2017 from ideastand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Folded Paper Ornaments 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/folded-paper-ornaments-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/folded-paper-ornaments-2021/</guid>
      <description>Fold a sheet of origami paper in half. That&amp;#039;s why i am excited to show you how to make your very own folded paper star christmas ornament! Fold green paper accordion style to create the look of christmas trees, adding paper ornaments to finish the look.
  PaperCrumpled0010 - Free Background Texture - paper folds fold grunge from www.textures.com  Just 4 sheets of square paper, folded and stuck together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Button Christmas Crafts 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/button-christmas-crafts-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/button-christmas-crafts-2021/</guid>
      <description>Great classy little projects to spice up your christmas or holiday season. Get ideas for family and kids&amp;#039; crafts at howstuffworks. Advertisement crafts at howstuffworks has hundreds of fun ideas to keep your family entertained.
  40+ Easy And Cheap DIY Christmas Crafts Kids Can Make | Architecture from cdn.architecturendesign.net  These crafts will let you explore your creative side. By gatheringbeauty in clay by mayb in clay by my stamp lady i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sustainable Christmas Decorations 2021</title>
      <link>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/sustainable-christmas-decorations-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelcgrady.github.io/post/sustainable-christmas-decorations-2021/</guid>
      <description>This is the simplest christmas decor, and looks great, whether it is in a window, or on your bathroom counter. Get your space ready for the holidays with the best christmas décor ideas. Deck the halls with these affordable (and adorable!) christmas decorations.
  40 Beautiful Christmas Painting Ideas to Try This Season - Bored Art from www.boredart.com  Here&amp;#039;s how to decorate for christmas with ornaments you&amp;#039;re not using.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
